{"courses": [
        {"id": 1,
            "title": "Kurs Języka Angielskiego",
            "lessons": [
                {"id": 1,
                    "title": "Lekcja 1: Podstawowe słowa",
                    "flashcards": [
                        {"question": "Hello","answer": "Cześć"},
                        {"question": "Goodbye","answer": "Do widzenia"}
                    ]},
                {"id": 2,
                    "title": "Lekcja 2: Kolory",
                    "flashcards": [
                        {"question": "Red","answer": "Czerwony"},
                        {"question": "Blue","answer": "Niebieski"}
                    ]},
                {"id": 3,
                    "title": "Lekcja 3: Doulingo",
                    "flashcards": [
                        {"question": "Hello","answer": "Cześć"},
                        {"question": "connectors","answer": "złącza"},
                        {"question": "preferable","answer": "lepszy, preferowany"},
                        {"question": "footprints","answer": "ślady stóp, ślady"}
                    ]
                }
            ]},
        {"id": 2,
            "title": "Kurs Języka Włoskiego",
            "lessons": [
                {"id": 1,
                    "title": "Lekcja 1: Podstawowe zwroty",
                    "flashcards": [
                        {"question": "Buongiorno","answer": "Dzień dobry"},
                        {"question": "Arrivederci","answer": "Do widzenia"}
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}